<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Courses on UTSEUS</title><link>https://shu-utseus.github.io/courses/</link><description>Recent content in Courses on UTSEUS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shu-utseus.github.io/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data-Science</title><link>https://shu-utseus.github.io/courses/data-science/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://shu-utseus.github.io/courses/data-science/</guid><description>Introduction This is a data science course. Data science is a multidisciplinary field that uses scientific methods, processes, algorithms, and systems to extract knowledge and insights from structured and unstructured data. In this course, students will learn about the principles, techniques, and tools used in data science.
Course Objectives Understand the fundamentals of data science, including data collection, cleaning, and analysis. Learn about statistical methods and machine learning algorithms used in data science.</description></item><item><title>Deep-learning</title><link>https://shu-utseus.github.io/courses/deep-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://shu-utseus.github.io/courses/deep-learning/</guid><description>Introduction This is a deep learning course. Deep learning is a subfield of machine learning that focuses on algorithms inspired by the structure and function of the brain&amp;rsquo;s neural networks. In this course, students will learn about the principles, algorithms, and applications of deep learning.
Course Objectives Understand the fundamentals of deep learning, including neural networks and their architectures. Learn about advanced deep learning techniques, such as convolutional neural networks (CNNs) and recurrent neural networks (RNNs).</description></item><item><title>Machine-learning</title><link>https://shu-utseus.github.io/courses/machine-learning/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 07:07:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://shu-utseus.github.io/courses/machine-learning/</guid><description>Introduction This is a machine learning course. Machine learning is a field of artificial intelligence that focuses on the development of algorithms that enable computers to learn from and make predictions or decisions based on data. In this course, students will learn about the fundamentals, algorithms, and applications of machine learning.
Course Objectives Understand the basic concepts and principles of machine learning. Learn about different types of machine learning algorithms, such as supervised, unsupervised, and reinforcement learning.</description></item></channel></rss>